梁繼昌議員。
Acting president.
反對嘅請舉手。
在House Committee Meeting held on 4 November 2016.
成員決定成立一個小委員會，來審查修訂通知。
我 move that the motion under my name, as printed on the agenda, be passed.
With these remarks, acting president, I urge members to support the motion. Thank you.
to allow sufficient time for the subcommittee to report its deliberations to the house committee.
The subcommittee held a meeting on 15 November 2016 with the administration to examine the amendment notice.
我現在向各位提出嘅代決議題係梁繼昌議員動議嘅議案，予以通過。有冇議員想發言？
In my capacity as chairman of this committee on inland revenue, amendment of Schedule 17E, Notice 2016.
我現在向各位提出嘅代決議題係梁繼昌議員動議嘅議案，予以通過。現在附附諸表決，贊成嘅請舉手。
我call upon members to support the motion on extending the period for scrutinising the subsidiary legislation to 11 January 2017.
我認為議題獲得經由功能組別產生、選舉產生及分區直接選舉產生嘅兩部分在席議員分別以過半數贊成，我宣佈議案獲得通過。
議員議案，根據《釋義及通則條例》，就延展於二零一六年十一月二號提交本會審覽嘅《二零一六年税務條例修訂附表十七》I公佈嘅修訂期限而動議嘅異議決議案，我現在請梁繼昌議員發言及動議議案。